merapakistan.tv 2015-09-29

# Privacy Policy

* * *

PRIVACY POLICY

  * Third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user's prior visits to your website.
  * Google's use of the DART cookie enables it and its partners to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and/or other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [advertising opt-out page](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). (Alternatively, you can direct users to opt out of a third-party vendor's use of cookies by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative [opt-out page](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).)

**Privacy Policy for www.merapakistan.tv**

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by email at info@merapakistan.tv

MeraPakistan.Tv respects your right to privacy. As part of the registration process, we give you the opportunity to decline to receive any mailings from either MeraPakistan.Tv or other parties to whom MeraPakistan.Tv may provide such information.

The data we collect from the web site is used in the aggregate to give us demographic information about the entire MeraPakistan.Tv audience in order to improve the MeraPakistan.Tv service. The personal information you provide - name, email address, etc. -- allows us to inform you about updates to the service and to notify you of products and services of MeraPakistan.Tv and its affiliates.

MeraPakistan.Tv does share non-personal, non-individual information in aggregate form with third parties for business purposes. For example, we may tell our business partners how many customers in certain demographic groups sent certain cards.

When you send one of our cards, the information you provide to us is used to customize your greeting with the recipient's name and with your message, and to deliver an email notification to the recipient. We treat our cards as private correspondence between the sender and the recipient and will not disclose the contents of a card, other than to the intended recipient, unless we are required to do so by law or we in good faith believe that such action is necessary to (1) comply with the law or with legal process; (2) protect and defend our rights and property; (3) protect against misuse or unauthorized use of MeraPakistan.Tv ; or (4) protect the personal safety or property of our users or the public. However, if you provide a false email address or attempt to pose as someone else when sending a card, information about you - including your computer's IP address - may be disclosed as part of any investigation into your actions.

Under normal circumstances, we will not monitor or edit the contents of the cards you send. On occasion, however, MeraPakistan.Tv personnel may need to view your message in connection with the technical processing of your greeting or the maintenance of our network. Also, if you ask one of our customer service representatives to help you send a card or to verify that a card was sent, that representative will be able to access all information about the card, including the recipient's email address and the message.

MeraPakistan.Tv uses reasonable precautions to keep the personal information disclosed to us secure and to disclose such information only to third parties we believe to be responsible. However, we are not responsible for any breach of security or for any actions of any third parties which receive the information. MeraPakistan.Tv also links to a wide variety of other Pakistani/International sites. We are not responsible for their privacy policies or how they treat information about their users.

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/).

Related Posts

Top Rated Posts

Categories

Sponsor
